current-rms.com 2016-10-21

# Privacy Policy | Current

###  1\. WHO WE ARE 

We are Insphire Limited. Our company number is 3309635 and our registered address is 5 Chase Park, Daleside Road, Nottingham NG2 4GT UNITED KINGDOM (" **inspHire** ", " **Current RMS** ", " **we** ", " **us** ") 

###  2\. STATEMENT OF PRIVACY AND ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY 

2.1 Current RMS is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This is our privacy policy (the " **Privacy Policy** ") and it applies when you use our website current-rms.com and all other connected Current RMS websites worldwide (the " **Sites** "). 

2.2 This Privacy Policy governs the collection and usage by us of your personal information (this means any information which personally identifies you e.g. your e-mail address, name, home address, work address or telephone number etc) (your " **Personal Data** "). By using the Sites, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

###  3\. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

What will Current RMS do with my Personal Data? 

3.1 Current RMS collects and processes your Personal Data for the following purposes: 

3.1.1 Current RMS service updates   
Current RMS may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues, product surveys, new feature announcements and news about Current RMS products and services. These e-mails are considered essential to the provision of the service you have requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered a part of the service you have chosen. 

3.1.2 Marketing and research   
Current RMS may use your Personal Data to inform you of other products or services available from Current RMS. For information on how to limit or stop any such communications, see the below section titled " **Control of your Personal Data** ". 

3.2 Current RMS may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your experience and opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. For information on how to limit or stop any such communications, see the below section titled " **Control of your Personal Data** ". 

3.3 Control of your Personal Data   
You may stop the delivery of future promotional e-mails from Current RMS by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. The instructions explain how to stop receiving such e-mails. 

3.4 Who will Current RMS share my Personal Data with?   
Current RMS does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Current RMS will share your Personal Data with the following third parties (such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Data except to provide these services to Current RMS); 

3.4.1 Current RMS’s operational service partners in order to operate the Sites and deliver the services you have requested; and/or 

3.4.2 with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, or provide customer support. 

3.5 Current RMS will not disclose your Personal Data to any other third parties without your consent unless required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

3.5.1 conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Current RMS or the Sites; 

3.5.2 protect and defend the rights or property of Current RMS and/or the Sites; and 

3.5.3 act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Sites. 

3.6 Please keep in mind that if you publicly disclose Personal Data through our Sites, we are not responsible for the security of the Personal Data you publicly disclose and it may be collected and used by others. 

3.7 Current RMS encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the Sites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Current RMS is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites it may link to. 

###  4\. Current RMS TRANSACTIONAL DATA RETENTION POLICY 

Upon termination of your subscription with Current RMS any transactional information provided by you to Current RMS will be retained for a period of 6 (six) months from the date your subscription terminates before being securely deleted. As an additional courtesy, at our discretion, we will aim to give 1 (one) month’s notice of this deletion. During the period between termination and deletion of the data you may request an export file of a copy of a limited subset of your unformatted transactional data. A nominal administration fee may be charged for this service. 

###  5\. SUBJECT ACCESS REQUESTS 

If you wish to find out what Personal Data we hold about you, you can make a subject access request under the Data Protection Act 1998. Your request must be in writing and should detail the nature and likely location of your Personal Data, along with proof of ID and payment of the relevant fee (currently £10). You should send your request to us at hello@current-rms.com and we will provide you with an address to write. 

###  6\. USE OF COOKIES 

6.1 Current RMS uses " **cookies** " to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to enhance your user experience. You can obtain information about how to manage cookies at www.aboutcookies.org. 

6.2 Current RMS keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within our Sites in order to determine which services and facilities are the most popular. Any Personal Data collected in this way may be used to deliver customised content and advertising within the Current RMS business to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

6.3 There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Current RMS. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used by Current RMS for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Sites. 

6.4 You have the ability to accept or decline cookies through your browser settings. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to use our Site. 

6.5 We are aware of the EU Directive 2009/136/EC, which came into force on 26 May 2011. We are currently reviewing this Privacy Policy and considering how best to implement any changes required to the way that cookies are used on the Sites. 

###  7\. SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

7.1 Current RMS secures your Personal Data from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. Current RMS secures the Personal Data you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. When Personal Data is transmitted over the internet it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

7.2 For the purposes of data processing, the information and Personal Data you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside of the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). This may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside the EEA, or if one of our service providers is located in a country outside the EEA. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. 

7.3 In addition, if you use our services while you are outside the EEA, your Personal Data may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with those services. 

###  8\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Current RMS is protecting your Personal Data. 

###  9\. CONTACT INFORMATION 

Current RMS welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about Current RMS or this Privacy Policy, please contact Current RMS by e-mail at: hello@current-rms.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
